Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1950-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Arena Stage audiovisual, 1980s-1990s; 6 linear ft. (7 boxes)
  - CSP Rap master tape (Box 5)
  - CSP Rap original (Box 5)
  - Living Stage, Hope Rap 1989 (Box 5)
  - Living Stage, Hope Rap 1989 (Box 5)
  - Living Stage, Freedom Rap, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Living Stage, Violence Rap, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Misc. Living Stage raps 1987 (Box 5)
  - Living Stage, rap on violence 1987 (Box 5)
    2 audio cassette
  - Living Stage, Freedom Rap, 1985 (Box 5)
  - misc. Living Stage rap, 1987 (Box 5)
  - ADASA Jams 1988 (Box 5)
  - ADASA Jams dubed orignial, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Ghosts Acts I and II, undated (Box 6-7)
  - First Lady Benefit, March 16, 1998 (Box 6-7)
  - Hedda Gabler, February 12, 1995 (Box 6-7)
  - Dimly... Acts I and II, undated (Box 6-7)
  - Dance of Death Acts I and II, undated (Box 6-7)
  - Dance of Death Acts I and II, 1995-1996 (Box 6-7)
  - Dancing at Lughnasa Acts I and II, November 13, 1993 (Box 6-7)
  - Dancing at Lughnasa, September 30, 1993 (Box 6-7)
  - Fires in the Mirror PBS, undated (Box 6-7)
  - Fires in the Mirror Matinee, September 18, 1993 (Box 6-7)
  - The Faraway Nearby Matinee Parts I-III, December 19, 1998 (Box 6-7)
  - Expecting Isabel Evening Acts I and II, November 21, 1998 (Box 6-7)
  - A Community Carol Acts I and II, January 2, 1994 (Box 6-7)
  - A Community Carol Rehearsal Run, undated (Box 6-7)
  - Coming of the Hurricane Acts I and II, undated (Box 6-7)
  - Playquest '94: Dirtywork, January 30, 1994 (Box 6-7)
  - All My Sons Acts I and II, May 28, 2000 (Box 6-7)
  - Almost Blue, January 15, 1995 (Box 6-7)
  - Animal Crackers Acts I and II, April 10, 1999 (Box 6-7)
  - Arcadia Acts I and II, January 18, 1997 (Box 6-7)
  - Black No More Acts I and II, 1997-1998 (Box 6-7)
  - Blithe Spirit Acts I and II, undated (Box 6-7)
  - Blues for an Alabama Sky Acts I and II, 1996-1997 (Box 6-7)
  - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof Final Preview Acts I and II, September 17, 1998 (Box 6-7)
  - Candide, April 27, 1996 (Box 6-7)
  - A Month in the Country Acts I and II, undated (Box 6-7)
  - The Odyssey Acts I and II, October 9, 1994 (Box 6-7)
  - A Perfect Ganesh Acts I and II, September 17, 1994 (Box 6-7)
  - The Plough and the Stars Acts I-IV, 1995-1996 (Box 6-7)
  - Old Dog, New Tricks Coyote Research, 2000-2001 (Box 6-7)
  - The Skin of Our Teeth Acts I-III, undated (Box 6-7)
  - The Royal Family Acts I-III, October 1999 (Box 6-7)
  - The Price Acts I and II, January 30, 1994 (Box 6-7)
  - Revengers' Comedies Acts I-IV, April 23, 1994 (Box 6-7)
  - Playquest: Sin, February 27, 1994 (Box 6-7)
  - A Room of One's Own, June 8, 1994 (Box 6-7)
  - Holiday Heart Acts I and II, October 10, 1995 (Box 6-7)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing, September 11, 1999 (Box 6-7)
  - How I Learned to Drive, May 1, 1999 (Box 6-7)
  - House Arrest Acts I and II, December 27, 1997 (Box 6-7)
  - I am a Man Acts I and II, April 1995 (Box 6-7)
  - Life Go Boom!, 1994-1995 (Box 6-7)
  - Let Em Eat Cake Benefit, 1995 (Box 6-7)
  - Long Day's Acts I-IV, undated (Box 6-7)
  - The Matchmaker Acts I-IV, undated (Box 6-7)
  - Love and Executioners, March 28, 1998 (Box 6-7)
  - Miracle Worker Acts I-III, undated (Box 6-7)
  - The Miser Parts I and II, undated (Box 6-7)
  - Oak and Ivy, February 18, 1999 (Box 6-7)
  - Molly Sweeney Acts I and II, February 25, 1997 (Box 6-7)
- Arena Stage records Acc. 2008-004, 2010-003, 1950s-2006
  Acc. 2008-004 consists of Zelda Fichandler speeches, files, Living Stage documents, correspondence, red books, and scripts. Hard copy inventory in Arena Stage accession folder. Acc. 2010-003 consists of 1 box of files, correspondence, speeches, scripts, and some photographs. Also includes extensive material on Awake and Sing, and the speeches date from 1968 until 2004.
  An electronic box inventory is unavailable. Please contact speccoll@gmu.edu for more information.
- Accession 2008-018, 1996-2007
  9 boxes of research packets from plays that also include various script drafts, some by Sarah Ruhl. Some folders also contain correspondence. File folders and loose materials were removed from larger brown folders with photocopy of discarded brown folder labels. Audiovisual and electronic records removed from paper records and placed in separate document box. Separation sheets identify original location.
  - Passion Play, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    3 folders
  - Molly's "Passion" Old Version, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
    2 folders
  - DC Christmas Carol Research Packet, November 2006 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Christmas Carol 1941, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
  - Christmas Carol 1941 Actor's Packet (Copy 1), 2007 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
  - Christmas Carol 1941 Actor's Packet (Copy 2), 2007 (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
  - DC Carol Correspondence, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
  - DC Christmas Carol Research Packet Part Three, September 2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    1 folder
  - Molly's Script Oldest Passion Play, November 23, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
  - Passion Play Research Packet, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
  - DC Christmas Carol Research Packet Part Two, November 2006 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - DC Christmas Carol Research Packet Part One, November 2006 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Passion Play, Copy Date January 22, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Passion Play A Cycle by Sara Ruhl, Copy Date June 13, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Clean House by Sara Ruhl, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Passion Play, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - Passion Play Notes, 2005? (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Passion Play, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 12-14)
  - Passion Play, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
  - Oak and Ivy, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17-20)
    4 folders
  - The Women of Brewster Place, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 21-22)
  - Anna Christie, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Passion Play A Cycle Actor's Packet, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 3-5)
  - Well Research Packet, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 6-8)
  - Molly's Brewster Notes, The Women of Brewster Place, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Cuttin-Up: Wit and Wisdom Inside Black Barber Shops, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The Women of Brewster Place Research Packet, Summer 2007 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
  - Ella Research Packet, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
  - Arthur Miller Festival Research Packet, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 15-17)
  - 33 Variations Research Packet, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 33 Variations Research Packet, March 2007 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 33 Variations Research Packet, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
  - 33 Variations Final Script, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 33 Variations La Jolla Draft, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 33 Variations Index, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 6-9)
  - 33 Variations Research Packet, September 2006 (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
  - 33 Variations Research Packet, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof Research, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Library of Congress Research, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 14-15)
  - Oak and Ivy, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Oak and Ivy, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - The Cocoanuts Scripts and Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Animal Crackers Scripts, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Animal Crackers Scripts, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Cabaret Master Articles, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Master Cabaret Articles, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
  - You Can't Take It With You Script and Production Guides, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - You Can't Take It With You Research Notes and Clippings, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
  - Uncle Vanya Research, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 9-14)
    6 folders
  - Dimly Perceived Theatre to the System Clippings, Guides, and Scripts, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
  - Dimly Perceived Theatre to the System Clippings, Guides, and Scripts, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - First Lady Playbills and Script, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Lovers and Executions Scripts, Guides, and Research, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 3-8)
  - Black No More Notes and Guides, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 9-11)
  - Black No More Script Drafts, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 12-18)
    7 folders
  - House Arrest Mark Taper Forum Production Draft, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 19-21)
  - House Arrest First Edition, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 1-8)
    8 folders
  - A Touch of the Poet Reviews, Scripts, and Guides, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
  - A Touch of the Poet Scripts and Research, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 11-14)
  - A Touch of the Poet Scripts and Research, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Room Service Scripts, Guides, and Clippings, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 3-5)
  - Animal Crackers Scripts and Research, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
  - Animal Crackers Scripts and Research, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 8-9)
  - How I Learned to Drive Scripts and Research, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
  - DVDs, Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - CD-Rs, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Arena Stage artistic personnel, 1950-2000; 9.5 linear feet (8 boxes)
  Collection contains head shots, resumes and brief biographies of artistic personnel at Arena Stage including actor, actress, set designers, directors, and lighting designers. Actors and actress of note include James Earl Jones, Christoper Guest, Yeardly Smith, Robert Prosky.
  - June Gable, actress (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Paul Gallo, lighting designer (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Victor Garber, actor (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Laura Gardner, actress (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Julie Garfield, actress (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jack Garfein, artistic director (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gale Garnett, actress (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Beulah Garrick, actress (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Larry Friedman, actor (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Andrea Frierson, actress (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Kate Fuglei, actress (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - George Furth, playwright (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Kent Foreman, poet-actor (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Henderson Forsythe, actor (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Francis Foster, actress (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Clarence Fontain and the Five Blind Boys of Alabama, musicians (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ed Fowler, actor (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Constance Fowlkes, actress (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Robert Foxworth, actor (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Mary Francell, actress (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Peter Francis-James, actor (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Richard Frank, actor (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gene Frankel, director (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Carl Franklin, actor (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Laurie Franks, actress (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Elizabeth Franz, actress (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Gina Franz, actress (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Mark Frawley, dancer (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Inga Frederick, dancer/actress (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Rita Fredricks, producer (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Morgan Freeman, actor (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Dorothea Frietag, composer (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Valerie French, actress (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Martin Fried, director (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Ronnie Farer, actress (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Michael Fairman, actor (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Jeff Fignar, actor (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - J.J. farley and the Original Soul Stirrers, band (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Kimberly Farr, actress (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Fred Fearing, subscriber (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Marjorie Feiner, actress (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Sarah Felcher, actress (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Clarence Felder, actor (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Lou Ferguson, actor (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Jay Frenandez, actor (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Conchatta Farrell, actress (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Geoffrey Ferris, director (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Robert Fields, actor (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - ASA program listing (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - John Finn, actor (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Linda Fisher, costume designer (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Robert Fisher, musical director and vocalist (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Niki Flacks, actress (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Louisa Flanighan, actress (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Pauline Flanagan, actress (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Walter Flanagan, actor (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Dingwall Fleary, musical consultant (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Jay Fletcher, actor (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Sandra Yen Fong, costume designer (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Clebert Ford, actor (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Hugh Estan, dancer (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Laura Esterman, actor (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Richard Estes, actor (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Christine Estabrook, actress (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - T.J. Escot, actor (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - richard Ericson, vocal consultant/associate artist (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - David Eric, actor (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Pierre Epstein, actor/director (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Benjamin Epps, actor (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Boni Enten, actress (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Tim Eyermann, composer (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Donald Ewer, actor (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Pamela Everett, dancer (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Tom Everett, actor (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Kurt Everhart, actor (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - David Evans, actor (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Beverly Emmons, lighting designer (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Donna Emmanuel (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Morris Engle, actor (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Woody Eney, actor (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Marianna Elliott, costume designer (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Rebecca Ellens, actor (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - John Elko, actor (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Eric Elice, actor (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Dana Elcai, actor (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Vladimir Ekzarkhov, actor (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Jill Eikenberry, actress (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Karl Eigsti, scenic designer (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Heather Ehlers, actress (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - William Eggleston, lighting designer (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Ryan Edwards, composer (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Beverly Edwards, actress (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Lars Edegman, musical director (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - George Ebeling, actor (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Charles Edwards, actor (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Jeannie Dougherty, actress (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Katherine Dowling, actress (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Herb Downer, actor (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Gilian Doyle, actor (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Donna Drake, singer/dancer/actress (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Elizebeth Duvall, actress (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Nancy Dutton, actor (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Le Clanche Du Rand, actor (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Augustine Dunn, actor (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Pamela Dunlap, actress (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Nora Dunfee, vocal consultant (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Tony Duncanson, actor (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Cara Duff-Maccormick, actress (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Jeanette Duboir, actress (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Donald Driver, actor (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Ronald Drake, actor (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Gillian Drake, actress (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Stanley R. Greenberg, playwright (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Linda Gregg, actress,musician,singer (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Gene Gross, actress (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Anne Grey, actor (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Joe Grifasi, actor (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Trevor Griffiths, actor (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - William Grimmett, actor (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - George Grizzard, actor (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - David Loyd Gropeman, actor (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Ron Parker, actor (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gordon Paddison, actor (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Louis padilla, actor (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Greg Pake actor (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Petronia Paley, actress (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ted Pappas, choreographer (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Theodor Pappas, movement consultant (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Joe Palmieri, actor (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Gerry Paone, actor (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Joan Pape, actress (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bernie Papure, actor (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sally Parker, musical director (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Shezwae Powell, actress (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Jill Powell, dancer (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Marion Swan, actress (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Anne Swift, actress (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Caroline Swift, actor (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Arlene Stern, actress (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - J.D. Steele Singers, musicians (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Kim Staunton, actress (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Arden Staroba, actor (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Katherine Squire, actress (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Kikolai G. Speransky, actor (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Alexander Spencer, actor (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Jeanne Sprague, actress (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Cary Anne Spear, actress (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - The Southeast Inspirational Choir, choir (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Vance Sorrells, musician/actor (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Phyllis Somerville, actress (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Anna Sokolow, choreographer (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Elizabeth Smith, voice consultant (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Doneger Smith, actor (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Glenn Scimonelli, actor/singer/dancer (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Richard Sanders, actor (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Sharon Sausbraum, actress (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Garrett Saunders, singer/actor (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Nanette Savard, actress (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Raynor Scheine, actor (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - John Scherer, actor (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Barbara Sohmers, actress (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Donna Snow, actress (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Yeardley Smith, actress (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Mollie Smith, actress (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Lee Smith, actor (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Lane Smith, actor (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Kelly Chauncey Smith, actor (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Paul Schierhoun, actor (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Joanne Schmoll, actress (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - William G. Schilling, actor (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Otto L. Schlesinger, actor (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Ned Schmidtke, actor (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - David A. Schnirman, sound designer (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Scott Schofield, actor (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Fontaine Syer, actor/assistant (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Marcellus Stewart, actor (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Marsha Stewart, actor (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - William Stewart, managing director (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Scott Stevenson, actor (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Roberta Stiem, actress (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Harold Stone, actor (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Tom Stoppard, actor (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Tony Straiges, scenic designer (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Henry Stram, actor (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - John Strasberg, actor (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Victor Strengau, actor (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Donald Sutton, actor (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Delores Sutton, actor (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Shepard Stradwick, actor (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Frederick Strother, actor (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Margaret Strucklett, actress (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Dan Strickler, actor (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Gail Strickland, actress (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Joy Bell Tauber, actress (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Eron Tabor, singer/actor/dancer (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Kristopher Tabori, actor (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Olga Talyn, actress (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Jessica Tandy, actress (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Christopher Tanner, fencing instructor (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Barbara tarbuck, actress (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Dennis Tate, actor (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Rebecca Taylor, actress (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Robert Taylor, set designer (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Glenn Taylor, actor (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Wally Taylor, actor (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Bob Telson, music composer (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Deborah Jean Templin, actress (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Cynthia Thole, actress (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Robert Thaler, actor (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - James Tolkan, actor (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Lily Tomlin, actress (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Rip Torn, actor (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - David Toney, actor (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - John Towey, actor (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Tony Todd, actor (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Carl Thoma, actor (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Evelyn Thomas, actress (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Chuck Thorpes, actress (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Kevin Tinghe, actor (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Laurence Tisch, NYU (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Barbara Tobias, actress (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Laurine Towler, actress (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Sy Travers, actor (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Warren K. Travis, actor (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Paula Trueman, actress (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - George Tsypin, set designer (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Kristi Tucher, actress (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Michael Tucker, actor (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Manu Tupou, actress (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Kathleen Turner, actress (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Keith Tyrone, dancer (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Joan Ulmer, actress (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Michael Valenti, composer (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Robert Van hoalen, actor (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Richard Venture, actor (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Aronld Victor, actor (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Emlyn Williams, actor (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Jack Eric Williams, actor (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Jacqueline Williams, actress (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Jobeth Williams, actress (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Michael Willis, actor (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Rudolf Willrich, actor (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Chrissy Wilzac, actress (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Eleanor D. Wilson, actress (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Theodore Wilson, actor (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Penelope Windust, actress (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Henry Winkler, actor (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Kevin Winkler, actor (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Mel Winkler, actor (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Maggie Winn-Jones, actress (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - William Vines, actor (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Jennifer Von Mayrhauser, actress (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Lou Walton, actor (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Jeffrey Wilkins, actors (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Kurt Wilhelm, costume designer (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - David William, director (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Ann Williams, actress (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Barnett Williams, actor (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Carl Williams Jr., music director (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Ellis E. Williams, actor (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Jan Greenfield, actress/assistant stage manager (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dennis Green, playwright (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mitchell Greenberg, actor (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Valerie Grear, actress (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Goodman Theatre, producer (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Lisa Goodman, actress (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Michael Gorrin, actor (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bradford Gott-Lin, actor (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Michael Govan, actor (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Grace Grant, actress (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ernest Graves, actor (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Lou Gilbert, actor (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - John Gillis, actor (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Joey ginza, acotr (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Paul Giovanni, composer/singer (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Aurthur Giron, actor (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Christopher Gladstone, actor (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Larry Gleister, actor (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - David Glenn, set designer (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Joe Glenn, actor (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Ralph Glickman, actor (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - John Glore (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - William Godsey, actor (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Kathleen Goldpaugh, actress (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Martin Goldsmith, actor (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Norman Gevanthor, director (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Michael Giannitti, lighting designer (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Charlotte Gibson, actress (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Linda Geiser, actress (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Michael Genet, actor (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Alex Gelman, interpreter and assistant director (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Deborah Genovieie, actress (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Mike Genovese, actor (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - John Getz, actor (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Michael Gates, actor (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Edmund Gaynes, actor (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - John Gegenhuber, actor (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - David Garrison, actor (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Jane Groves, actress (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Suzanne grossman, actress (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Robin Groves, actress (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Castulo Guerra, actor (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Christopher Haden Guest, actor (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Dea Guidobono, actress (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Ann Guilbert, actress (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Robert Guillume, actor (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Lee Guilliatt, actress (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Carol Gustafson, actress (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Eric House, actor (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - George Clark Hosmer, actor (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Donald Hotton, actor (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Ghretta Hynd, constume designer (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Barton Heyman, actor (Box 3, Folder 53)